Finding Aid for the Preston Sturges Papers LSC.1114
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Supplement
  - B
    - Bell, Monta., 10 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 17)
    - Bell, Monta., 9 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 18)
    - Ben., 10 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 19)
    - Benchley, Robert., 1 piece. (Box 97, Folder 20)
    - Benton, Kate Sturges., 7 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 21)
    - Benton, Rita., 10 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 22)
    - Beo - Blu., 13 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 23)
    - Biden, Edmund and Grace., 1930-1931.; 14 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 24)
    - Biden, Edmund and Grace., 1931-1932.; 12 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 25)
    - Biden, Edmund and Grace., 1933.; 14 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 26)
    - Biden, Edmund and Grace., 1931-1943.; 12 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 27)
    - Biden, Edmund S., 6 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 28)
    - Biden, Sydney., 1937-1939.; 11 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 29)
    - Biden, Sydney., 1939-1940.; 10 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 30)
    - Biden, Sydney., 1941-1945.; 5 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 31)
    - Blowitz, Bill., 1 piece. (Box 97, Folder 32)
    - Blumenthal, Dick., 1 piece. (Box 97, Folder 33)
    - Bo - Bu., 12 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 34)
    - Bo - Bu., 13 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 35)
    - Bolton, Whitney., 3 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 36)
    - Brackett, Charles., 1 piece. (Box 97, Folder 37)
    - Brand, Harry., 3 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 38)
    - Brandt & Brandt Dramatic Department, Incorporated., 6 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 39)
    - Bridge, Alan., 10 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 40)
    - Brown, George., 1 piece. (Box 97, Folder 41)
    - Buckingham, Kate Sturges., 12 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 42)
    - Buckingham, Kate Sturges., 14 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 43)
    - Bue - Buz., 7 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 44)
  - C
    - C., 11 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 45)
    - California Pictures Corporation., 14 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 46)
    - Central Casting Corporation., 3 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 47)
  - D
    - Da - De., 12 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Desti, Mary., 11 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Desti, Mary., 6 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Desti estate., 19 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Di - Du., 8 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Drackert, Harry., 10 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Dunning, Philip., 9 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - G
    - G., 9 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Gilchrist, Bianca., 12 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Gilchrist, Bianca., 10 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - Gordon, Mack., 1 piece. (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - Gordon, William L., 3 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - H
    - Ha - Hi., 7 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 13)
    - Henigson, Henry., 1944.; 10 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 14)
    - Henigson, Henry., 1944-1945.; 10 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 15)
    - Henigson, Henry., 1945.; 11 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 16)
    - Henigson, Henry, 1946., 10 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 17)
    - Henigson, Henry, 1946., 5 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 18)
    - Ho - Hu., 9 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 19)
    - Holloway, Sterling., 2 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 20)
    - Houseman, John., 1 piece. (Box 98, Folder 21)
    - Hughes, Howard., 5 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 22)
    - Hutton, Eleanor Post., n.d.; 16 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 23)
    - Hutton, Eleanor Post., 1929-1930.; 11 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 24)
    - Hutton, Eleanor Post., 1930.; 11 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 25)
    - Hutton, Eleanor Post., 1930.; 11 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 26)
    - Hutton, Eleanor Post., 1930.; 15 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 27)
    - Hutton, Eleanor Post., 1931.; 13 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 28)
    - Hutton, Eleanor Post., 1931.; 14 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 29)
    - Hutton, Eleanor Post., 1931.; 16 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 30)
    - Hutton, Eleanor Post., 1932.; ]2 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 31)
    - Hutton, Eleanor Post., 1932.; 15 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 32)
    - Hutton, Eleanor Post., 1933-1934.; 12 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 33)
    - Hutton, Eleanor Post., 1934-1939.; 5 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 34)
  - I
    - I., 3 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 35)
  - J
    - J., 5 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 36)
    - J.G. Bachmann Company Incorporated., 1 piece. (Box 98, Folder 37)
    - Jessel, George., 2 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 38)
    - Johnson, Julian., 7 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 39)
  - K
    - K., 13 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 40)
    - King, Henry., 2 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 41)
    - Klune, Raymond., 1 piece. (Box 98, Folder 42)
    - Knox, Alexander., 2 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 43)
  - L
    - L., 9 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 44)
    - Lang, Walter., 1 piece. (Box 98, Folder 45)
    - Laurel, Stan., 1 piece. (Box 98, Folder 46)
    - Lyon, Ben., 4 pieces. (Box 98, Folder 47)
  - Mc
    - Mc., 10 pieces. (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Mc., 6 pieces. (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - McCarey, Leo., 2 pieces. (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - McGuire, William Anthony., 1 piece. (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - MacMillan Company., 4 pieces. (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - M
    - Ma., 11 pieces. (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Ma., 12 pieces. (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Ma., 11 pieces. (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Malone, Dudley., 5 pieces. (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Mamoulian, Rouben., 2 pieces. (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Mankiewicz, Joseph., 1 piece. (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - Marbury, Elizabeth., 10 pieces. (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - Martin, Walter., 13 pieces. (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - Me., 13 pieces. (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - Mendl, Lady Elsie., 2 pieces. (Box 99, Folder 15)
    - Mi., 5 pieces. (Box 99, Folder 16)
    - Miller, Gilbert., 6 pieces. (Box 99, Folder 17)
    - Mo., 15 pieces. (Box 99, Folder 18)
    - Moore, Charles., 1 piece. (Box 99, Folder 19)
    - Motion Picture Association of America, Incorporated., 16 pieces. (Box 99, Folder 20)
    - Mowbray, Alan., 1 piece. (Box 99, Folder 21)
    - Mu., 6 pieces. (Box 99, Folder 22)
    - Mudge, Estelle., n.d.; 10 pieces. (Box 99, Folder 23)
    - Mudge, Estelle., n.d.; 10 pieces. (Box 99, Folder 24)
    - Mudge, Estelle., n.d.; 11 pieces. (Box 99, Folder 25)
    - Mudge, Estelle., n.d.; 7 pieces. (Box 99, Folder 26)
    - Mudge, Estelle., 1922.; 12 pieces. (Box 99, Folder 27)
    - Mudge, Estelle., 1922.; 10 pieces. (Box 99, Folder 28)
    - Mudge, Estelle., 1922.; 10 pieces. (Box 99, Folder 29)
    - Mudge, Estelle., 1922.; 10 pieces. (Box 99, Folder 30)
    - Mudge, Estelle., 1922.; 13 pieces. (Box 99, Folder 31)
    - Mudge, Estelle., 1928-1933.; 15 pieces. (Box 99, Folder 32)
    - Mudge. M. DeW., 2 pieces. (Box 99, Folder 33)
  - N
    - Na., 9 pieces. (Box 99, Folder 34)
    - Ne., 13 pieces. (Box 99, Folder 35)
    - Neumann, Kurt and Irma., 1 piece. (Box 99, Folder 36)
    - The New Yorker., 21 pieces. (Box 99, Folder 37)
    - Newberry, Barbara., 1 piece. (Box 99, Folder 38)
    - Ni - Nu., 8 pieces. (Box 99, Folder 39)
    - Noyes, David A., 8 pieces. (Box 99, Folder 40)
  - O
    - 0., 1 piece. (Box 99, Folder 41)
    - Ophuls, Max., 8 pieces. (Box 99, Folder 42)
    - Ophuls, Max., 21 pieces. (Box 99, Folder 43)
  - P
    - Pa., 9 pieces. (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Pacific Writers Yacht Club., 8 pieces. (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Pangborn, Franklin., 2 pieces. (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Paramount Pictures Incorporated., 11 pieces. (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Parisette, Mildred., 8 pieces. (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Parmer, Charles., 2 pieces. (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Paul Kohner Incorporated., 11 pieces. (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Payson, Alex., 4 pieces. (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Payson, Lavinia., 2 pieces. (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Pe., 9 pieces. (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - Pemberton, Brock., n.d.; 10 pieces. (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - Pemberton, Brock., 1929-1930.; 9 pieces. (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - Pemnerton, Brock., 1931.; 15 pieces. (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - Pemberton, Brock., 1931-1934.; 10 pieces. (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - Pemberton, Brock., 1934-1940.; 10 pieces. (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - Perlberg, William., 1 piece. (Box 100, Folder 16)
    - Perry, Margaret., 5 pieces. (Box 100, Folder 17)
    - Pf - Pu., 15 pieces. (Box 100, Folder 18)
    - Plympton, Louise., 4 pieces. (Box 100, Folder 19)
    - Potel, Vic., 1 piece. (Box 100, Folder 20)
    - Presnell, Robert., 2 pieces. (Box 100, Folder 21)
    - Pryor, Roger., 1 piece. (Box 100, Folder 22)
  - R
    - Ra - Re., 6 pieces. (Box 100, Folder 23)
    - Renanvant, George., 16 pieces. (Box 100, Folder 24)
    - Rh - R0., 12 pieces. (Box 100, Folder 25)
    - Rhinelander, Major T.J.O., 6 pieces. (Box 100, Folder 26)
    - Risking Robert., 2 pieces. (Box 100, Folder 27)
    - Rogers, Charles R., 1 piece. (Box 100, Folder 28)
    - Ru - Ry., 7 pieces. (Box 100, Folder 29)
  - S
    - S., 11 pieces. (Box 100, Folder 30)
    - Samuel French Incorporated., 15 pieces. (Box 100, Folder 31)
    - Schenck, Joseph., 1 piece. (Box 100, Folder 32)
    - Schreiber, Lew., 4 pieces. (Box 100, Folder 33)
    - Screen Directors' Guild., 7 pieces. (Box 100, Folder 34)
    - Steele, Freddie., 1 piece. (Box 100, Folder 35)
    - Sturges, Solomon., 13 pieces. (Box 100, Folder 36)
    - Sturges, Solomon., 9 pieces. (Box 100, Folder 37)
  - T
    - T., 6 pieces. (Box 100, Folder 38)
    - Twentieth Century-Fox Film Corporation., 13 pieces. (Box 100, Folder 39)
  - V
    - Vincent, Frank., 1 piece. (Box 100, Folder 40)
  - W
    - Wa., 14 pieces. (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Wallis, Hal., 3 pieces. (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Wassong George., 1 piece. (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - We., 10 pieces. (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - We - Wh., 12 pieces. (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Weatherbee, Hicks., 14 pieces. (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Weatherbee, Hicks., 14 pieces. (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Weil, Joseph., 1 piece. (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - West Side Asthma and Riding Club., 10 pieces. (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Whitely, Marion., 11 pieces. (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Whitely, Marion., 12 pieces. (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - Wi., 14 pieces. (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - William Morris Agency., 15 pieces. (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - William Morris Agency., 19 pieces. (Box 101, Folder 14)
    - Wilson, Lois., 1 piece. (Box 101, Folder 15)
    - Wo - Wr., 9 pieces. (Box 101, Folder 16)
    - Woolcott, Alexander., 2 pieces. (Box 101, Folder 17)
    - Woolf, Edgar Allan., 2 pieces. (Box 101, Folder 18)
    - Woolfan, Bertrand E., 7 pieces. (Box 101, Folder 19)
    - Wright, Loyd., 17 pieces. (Box 101, Folder 20)
    - Writers Club., 15 pieces. (Box 101, Folder 21)
    - Writers Club., 15 pieces. (Box 101, Folder 22)
    - Writers Club., 15 pieces. (Box 101, Folder 23)
    - Writers Club., 15 pieces. (Box 101, Folder 24)
    - Writers Club., 7 pieces. (Box 101, Folder 25)
    - Wyler, William., 10 pieces. (Box 101, Folder 26)
  - XYZ
    - Z., 5 pieces. (Box 101, Folder 27)
  - Unknown
    - Unknown., 12 pieces. (Box 101, Box 28)
    - Unknown., 10 pieces. (Box 101, Folder 29)
    - Unknown., 11 pieces. (Box 101, Folder 30)
    - Unknown., 11 pieces. (Box 101, Folder 31)
    - Unknown., 4 pieces. (Box 101, Folder 32)
- Production Scrapbooks
  Scrapbooks of ephemeral material, including news and magazine clippings, relating to Sturges' stage and motion picture productions.
  - The guinea pig (released ). Scrapbook covers., 1929 1928-1929. (Box 102)
  - Strictly dishonorable I, II, II (). Scrapbook covers., 1929 1929-1932.; (3 vol.). (Box 102)
  - Strictly dishonorable. Serialization from the New York Daily Mirror. (). Scrapbook covers., 1929 1931. (Box 102)
  - The well of romance; and Fast and loose (released ). Scrapbook covers., 1930 1930.; (in 1 volume). (Box 102)
  - Recapture (released ). Scrapbook covers., 1930 1930. (Box 102)
  - Child of Manhattan (released ). Scrapbook covers., 1932 1931-1932. (Box 102)
  - Child of Manhattan. Serialization from the New York Daily Mirror. (released ). Scrapbook covers., 1932 1932. (Box 103)
  - The power and the glory (released ). Scrapbook covers., 1933 1933-1934. (Box 103)
  - Thirty-day princess; and The good fairy (released ). Scrapbook covers., 1934 1934-1935. (Box 103)
  - Spinster dinner; Song of joy; One rainy afternoon; Paris in the evening; Hotel Haywire; Easy living; If I were king; Port of the seven seas; Never say die; and McGinty. Scrapbook covers., 1935-1938. (Box 103)
  - Remember the night; and The great McGinty (released ). Scrapbook covers., 1940 1939-1940. (Box 103)
  - The great McGinty (released ). Scrapbook covers., 1940 1940-1941. (Box 103)
  - The great McGinty; and Christmas in July (released ). Scrapbook covers., 1940 1940-1941. (Box 104)
  - Christmas in July (released ). Scrapbook covers., 1940 1940-1941. (Box 104)
  - The lady Eve I and II (released ). Scrapbook covers., 1941 1940-1942.; (2 vol.). (Box 104)
  - Sullivan's travels I and II (released ). Scrapbook covers., 1941 1941-1948.; (2 vol.). (Box 104)
  - Palm Beach story (released ). Scrapbook covers., 1942 1941-1943. (Box 105)
  - I married a witch (released ). Scrapbook covers., 1942 1941-1942. (Box 105)
  - The great moment (released ). Scrapbook covers., 1944 1942-1944. (Box 105)
  - Hail the conquering hero (released ). Scrapbook covers., 1944 1943-1944. (Box 105)
  - Miracle of Morgan's Creek I and II (released ). Scrapbook covers., 1944 1942-1949.; (2 vol.). (Box 105)
  - Miracle of Morgan's Creek (released ). Scrapbook covers. (advertisements)., 1944 1944 (Box 105)
  - The sin of Harold Diddlebock -or- Mad Wednesday I and II (released ). Scrapbook covers., 1947 1944-1951.; (2 vol.). (Box 106)
  - Unfaithfully yours (released ). Scrapbook covers., 1948 1947-1948. (Box 106)
  - The beautiful blond from Bashful Bend (released ). Scrapbook covers., 1949 1947-1949. (Box 106)
  - Make a wish (released ). Scrapbook covers., 1951 1951. (Box 106)
  - Helicopter newsclippings relating to Sturges' interest in the vehicle., 1947. (Box 107)
  - Personal I., 1930-1944. (Box 107)
  - Personal II., 1941-1944. (Box 107)
  - Personal III., 1944-1948. (Box 107)
  - Personal IV., 1948-1951. (Box 107)
  - Strictly Dishonorable. Serialization in the New York Daily Mirror. (released ). Scrapbook covers., 1929 1931. (Box 109)
  - Child of Manhattan. Serialization in the New York Daily Mirror (released ). Scrapbook covers., 1932 1932. (Box 109)
  - Miracle of Morgan's Creek. Advertisements (released ). Scrapbook covers., 1944 1944 (Box 109)
- Boats., n.d.; 11 pieces. (Box 108)
  Photographs and diagrams.
- Child of Manhattan., ca. 1932.; 7 pieces. (Box 108)
  Publicity. Includes posters, programs, signs.
- Drawings., n.d.; Watercolor. 2 items. (Box 108)
- The Life of Christ by James R. Boone., 1936.; 2 pieces. (Box 108)
- Los Angeles Times., July 21, 1949. (Box 108)
  Clipping re Mickey Cohen.
- Menus., ca. 1951.; 41 pieces. (Box 108)
  Includes Players Restaurant menus and Sturges' notes.
- Music., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 108)
  Orchestration.
- Photographs., n.d.; 2 items. (Box 108)
- Players., ca. 1951.; 3 pieces. (Box 108)
  Advertisements.
- Playbills., n.d.; 15 pieces. (Box 108)
- Saturday Evening Post., March 15, 1941. (Box 108)
  Contains article on Sturges.
- Accession LSC-1114-2008-09 backlog material, LSC-1114-2008-09 (Box 109, Box 110, Box 111, Box 112, Box 113, Box 114, Box 115, Box 116, Box 117, Box 118, Box 119, Box 120, Box 121, Box 122, Box 123, Box 124, Box 125, Box 126, Box 127, Box 128, Box 129, Box 130, Box 131)
- Accession LSC-1114-2012-08 backlog material, LSC-1114-2012-08; 4 Born-digital Carriers (4 optical discs); 6 Audiovisual Carriers (6 videocassettes) (Box 1, Box 2, Box 132)